http://www.enablingbiz.com/privacy-statement.php

Privacy Statement
This privacy policy sets out how EnablingBiz ESolutions uses and protects any information that you give EnablingBiz ESolutions when you use this website.
We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
EnablingBiz ESolutions may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from February 16, 2010.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
Name and job title
Contact information including email address
Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
Information regarding your business and project requirements
Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
Develop commercial and technical project proposals for you.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
not filling up any of the customer requirement questionnaires
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for any purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [email address]
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to info@enablingbiz.com.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
All Site
Web Design ServicesSoftware DevelopmentMobile Application DevelopmentCorporate BrandingPHP-MySQL DevelopmentASP.NET DevelopmentContent DevelopmentInternet Marketing Services
Blog
Web Design
Application Development
Search Engine Marketing
Graphic Design
Portfolio
Blog
Company
Contact
Privacy | Disclaimer | T & C
Sitemap | XML
Art, Automobile, Designing & Development, Education, Government, Environment, Food, Gifts, Handicrafts, Industrial Machinery, IT-industry, Lawyer, Medical, NGO, Travel & tourism, Apparel, Consultant, Courier Services, Investigative, Electronics, Financial Services, Media, Paints, Real Estate
India, UK, USA, Taiwan, Greece, Italy, Australia, Netherlands, Germany, Japan, China
Internet Marketing | Website design firm India | Web Development company | Website designing firm
EnablingBiz
Mailing Address:212, Shivam HouseKarampura Commercial Complex, New Delhi 110015 India
Fax:+91-11-41443563
Yslow (A)             Google Page Speed (90)
ï¿½ Copyright 2010. EnablingBiz Esolutions, Delhi, India.
EnablingBiz ESolutions is an Internet Marketing, Bespoke Web Design & Web Application Development Firm
info@enablingbiz.com
Skype: Enablingbiz
UK: +44-121-2709465
Web Design ServicesInternet Marketing Services
Web Design ServicesHTML Website DesignCustom Web DesignBusiness Website DesignFlash Website DesignEcommerce Web DesignCMS Web DesignAccessible Web DesignCustom Blog DesignWeb Application DevelopmentRegister a domainManaged Web HostingHire Website Designer
Internet Marketing ServicesResearch & AnalyticsSocial Media MarketingEmail MarketingOnline Reputation ManagementAffiliate Marketing ServicesIndustry Specific SEOSEO ServicesLanding Page DesignWeb Advertising ServicesFacebook Page DesignInternet Marketing Consultancy
ASP.NET DevelopmentPHP-MySQL Development
ASP.NET DevelopmentAsp.net Application DevelopmentXML DevelopmentDot Net Nuke DevelopmentHire ASP.NET Programmer
PHP-MySQL DevelopmentCustom Web App DevelopmentBespoke Ecommerce DevelopmentAJAX DevelopmentMagento CustomizationOscommerce DevelopmentJoomla DevelopmentCake PHP DevelopmentJoomla CustomizationDrupal Web DevelopmentMambo DevelopmentZen Cart CustomizationX Cart IntegrationPHP LAMP DevelopmentHire PHP Developer
Corporate BrandingContent Development
Corporate BrandingCustom QR Code DesignCustom Logo DesignCorporate Brochure DesignMultimedia DVD DesignPrint Catalog DesignFlyer DesignCD Presentation DesignTrade Show Booth DesignCorporate VideoPDF Brochure DesignCorporate Screensaver DesignIllustration DesignEmail Letterhead DesignBusiness Stationery DesignAnimated Logo DesignSlogan DesignPrint Ad DesignAnnual Report DesignPoster DesignBanner DesignHire Graphic Designer
Content DevelopmentInfographic Design ServiceEmail Copywriting ServicesContent Writing ServicesDirect Mail Copywriting SEO-based Article Copywriting Brochure CopywritingCompany Profile CopywritingAdvertising CopywritingPress Release CopywritingBlog Copywriting
Software DevelopmentMobile Application Development
Software DevelopmentC# (C Sharp) DevelopmentC++ DevelopmentFlash Application DevelopmentFacebook Application DesignOffshore Software Development
Mobile Application DevelopmentMobile Web DevelopmentAndroid Application DevelopmentiPhone Application DevelopmentBlackberry App DevelopmentWindows Mobile App DevelopmentHire Mobile Developers
Company Profile
Portfolio
Our Clients
Capabilities
Blog
Process
Visit Us
Subscribe to Newsletter
